Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
You proposed me Bannerlordship in
return of my life.
And I propose you an honorable death,
Balgay.
Commander Balgay. How did Osman know
we would be coming here?
I will figure that out before I cut his
tongue, Kongar.
Just as you scared so many people, try to
scare me with your sword now!
I am going to rip your heart, Osman!
Soldiers!
Prepare to die!
For Elhan!
Elhan, hear us roar!
With the help of Allah!
My mother and father will finally find
peace today, Kongar!
Let our armors be hard, let our sword
be sharp.
And let your head fall onto ground.
Ambush huh? You forgot the spite of
Mongols very fast, Samsa.
Balgay will also make you pay for this.
It’s time for Balgay to save himself from
Osman Bey’s claws right now.
You better mind your own business,
Cerkutay!
You Cerkutay, you!
Cetinalp!
Take two Alps with you!
And follow this dog wherever he goes...
…and kill him.
Go now!
Cerkutay must have had more of his dogs
on his side…
…it’s obvious his dogs are with Balgay
now.
We need to help Osman Bey as soon as
possible. Let’s go!
If I die before I make Kayis go extinct…
…let me burn in Eylikhan’s hell!
I will be your own hell.
Osman!
I came here to take your life, Osman!
To take your life!
Uncle?
Your death has arrived, Osman.
What's the matter?
Your half-father is here.
Aren’t you happy, Osman?
You killed my son, my Batur. Osman!
You shed the blood of your own kin in
Tent of Suleiman Sheikh!
Drown in your own blood!
Die!
What would you tell me if you had seen my
condition right now, son?
My arms and wings are broken while there
is a constant fire burning inside me.
Would say stay strong mother if you
had seen me right now?
How can I stay strong in a situation
like this, my child?
I wish you had not try to find Gunduz.
I wish my tongue had fallen off.
It was all for protecting, my little one.
Or else, how could I sacrifice you?
I only meant to protect and watch over.
My heart is on fire, my son.
I just can’t make head or tail of it.
Why would Osman kill my Batur brother?
There is neither proof nor witness.
Aygul!
Don’t you know Osman?
He killed your brother.
Are you still in love with him?
Huh?
If so, I hope your heart rots, Aygul!
Let your heart rot!
He was the same.
Osman was the same when he was growing up.
He would just do whatever he wanted to do.
Neither his father nor my Dundar managed
to restrain him.
I have been constantly telling he would
bring our end but nobody listened to me.
Whatever happened only happened to my son.
Bamsi.
Abdurrahman.
Gunduz.
Selcan.
All supported him.
They did not let anybody say anything.
They did not let any dust fall upon his
character.
At the end, they all made my son lose his
life.
However, they always protected Osman.
Do I have your permission, Zohre Hatun?
Come in.
Selcan and Gonca Hatun have just had their
horses be ready.
They are leaving the Tent.
Is that so?
Wow, Selcan Hatun. Wow!
Untill your blood spills...
…let burying my son be illicit for me.
Mother!
I beg you please act yourself!
Don’t speak!
Go arm yourself!
They killed my Batur, of course they will
drown in their own blood.
Get up!
That parasite will pay for my son’s life!
I’ll revenge my Batur's blood...
...with his own sword.
Mother!
Selcan Hatun has Alps.
What do you think we can do?
Please don’t do it.
Don’t we have our own Alps?
Go and let the Alps know.
Prepare the horses.
We will follow them.
Mother!
I told you to arm yourself!
I can not rest until that woman spits
blood.
Go now!
Samsa!
Come on Valiants!
Kill them all and don’t spare their lives!
Be with us Allah!
You will die, Osman!
You got away again!
Osman!
Drown in your blood, Osman!
Osman.
Genghis Khan says who he fights knowing
he will lose is a fool.
Come!
Konur!
Follow Balgay!
Dear or alive, I want both of them.
Go!
Uncle.
Uncle!
Dundar Bey!
Osman...
...I will be the one who brings your end.
Yet, Dundar Bey is dead.
He should not die, Melik.
He should not!
I need Dundar.
We must make sure!
Osman!
I will rip you with my own hands when
the time comes.
If Zohre Hatun learns that we left
the Tent, she will follow us.
We are close to Kurgan Valley.
If she's coming, she will see.
Come on, there is no rest for the weary.
They are going towards Kurgan Valley.
We will ambush them.
Mother, please don’t.
Let’s head back.
We left my brother in the Tent.
Please don’t.
You go back.
I will be seeking the revenge of my son.
I won’t come back until I kill them.
Now, listen to me carefully.
From now on, we will continue our road
with our swords.
Selcan Hatun is one of the stooges of
your Batur Bey’s, my son’s killer.
Today is the day for revenge.
There is no going back before we cut their
breaths.
Let’s go!
They are following us, Commander Balgay.
You are wounded, we need to lose our
track.
Warm water will make us lose our track…
…but not our hatred.
They used this water to lose their track.
We can’t go back unless we find them.
We need to keep searching for them.
My brother, you will leave them to me once
we find them.
For what?
Do you think I will go crazy and comply
with him again?
I know this time he will not bother
to kill, my Kongar.
And I don’t want you to go into brother
massacre.
He is not my brother.
His blood is helal since they stabbed my
father in the back and ravaged our Tent.
Speak now.
Speak.
What happened to Batur?
Huh?
You ask as if you don’t know already.
You killed Batur and sent his body
to Tent with a horse.
What else are you asking?
My Osman, what is he saying?
I don’t understand.
I don’t understand, Bamsi Bey, but
we will, eventually.
What important right now is Dundar Bey. He
is alive and what he tells us matters.
So, he still has a lot to suffer.
His soldiers are alive also.
Abdurrahman Ghazi, take Erkut and Kılıç
with you.
And take Dündar
Bey along with these two to Elif Mother.
The cave is close to Hawk Rocks.
- We will be there within a short time.
- But...
My uncle has to live. You
understand it, right?
Don’t you worry, my Osman.
The dog who killed Batur and set Dündar
Bey against us is the same person.
We can only learn whichever
dog it is from Dundar Bey.
- Come on, build a sledge!
- As you wish, my Bey.
Now, come here!
Who told you that we were here?
Who?
Speak!
Somebody you haven’t seen before.
- Who sent you?
- Balgay sent me, Dündar Bey.
- What does he want?
- Balgay knows where Osman is.
He is at Uhud Hills and
asks for your presence.
It is not Balgay who sent Dündar
Bey, huh my Osman?
Then who made Dundar Bey follow Balgay?
The one who shot Dundar Bey
with that arrow, Samsa Bey.
It is obvious somebody is trying all he
can to make me and my uncle enemies.
It’s neither Balgay...
...nor Yannis.
Sooner or later, we will
find who that traitor is.
But how are we going to do that, my Osman?
We will go to Tent and take
my father’s consignations.
Until today, Kayı
Tent has never been without a ruler.
And from now, it will not ever again.
We will not stop until we make
the ones who stepped on...
our customs and betrayed us
pay for what they did.
Praise be, my lion.
- Allahu Akbar!
Come on. We
shouldn't be afraid, Gonca.
I worry about you, Selcan Hatun. I have to
protect you.
I am an old girl, I always
take precautions.
Don't worry. Come on.
I swear that...
Kayıs' blood will flow like this stream.
I swear on the flying bird...
Kayıs' leader will fly like this.
I swear on the land...
the land will be full of dead people.
How could Osman set a
trap, Commander Balgay?
Don't you get it? They set me
a trap with Yannis.
Sneaky like a snake,
crafty like a fox.
A novice boy and an old
imbecile set me a trap.
You promised Yannis more than he deserved.
Why did Yannis betray you?
My promises were killed
by Osman's weapon, Kongar.
Let's find a cave and take shelter.
We should gain power.
Osman will understand that
Balgay isn't defeated.
Did you find Sofia?
We're still looking, sir.
If you can't find Sofia, you know
what's going to happen to you.
Yes, sir. I know.
No, you can't even imagine
what I'll do to you.
Sir, we looked at everywhere. It's like...
Shut up!
Did Osman...
kill Balgay?
There are many dead Mongols in Uhud
Hills and İnegöl borders.
But Balgay isn't one of them.
If Osman fails to keep Balgay, Mongols
will make us pay for it.
We've been played by Osman.
This trap will be our death, I'm afraid.
- Protect yourself!
- Zöhre Hatun!
What is it, Zöhre?
Are you a bandit now? Or a looter?
Osman killed my son.
And you helped him.
You'll pay for it, Hatun!
Batur died because of your evilness.
I thought you were smart. But, are you
being like your mother now?
I belong to my mother's side.
Do you think I won't take my
brother's revenge?
I understand. They want blood.
I'll kill you, Selcan Hatun.
Drop your weapon, Selcan Hatun.
Come on, let's hope that your
Osman will save you.
We hoped for one, but Allah gave us two.
The ones who we wish to be dead
are facing us, mother!
It's more fair, Zöhre Hatun!
Come on, Alps!
Ya Allah!
Dündar Bey will make his aides treat.
Osman punished me, by keeping Balgay.
I'll save Dündar and do what
Balgay can't do.
I'll kill Osman.
I'll have both Dündar and the Kayıs.
Tell me about your betrayal, Zöhre.
It's not over yet, Hatun.
Dündar Bey will call you to account.
Dündar Bey drowned in his treason.
I killed him, Zöhre Hatun.
Father.
Dündar.
You killed both my son and husband, Osman.
Dündar Bey and Batur collaborated
Mongols and Balgay.
They betrayed Kayıs.
Did you think I'd let traitors live?
The Bey of our tent is still my father.
No one can disobey our morals and our Bey.
Tell everyone...
I killed Dündar Bey myself.
Murderer.
Take Zöhre Hatun to the tent.
To the cage.
I have a bone to pick with her.
Let me go!
You'll get your deserts, Osman!
You killed my father and brother.
Murderer. Shame on you!
Shame on you!
Take Aygül too.
Come on.
Zülfikar Dervish, take my
brother to the tent.
Listen to me now.
Abdurrahman Ghazi! Dündar Bey!
Dündar!
He's in a bad condition. We
need to stop bleeding.
Build a fire.
We need to take the arrow out.
Give me the dagger.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. ( in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
O The Healer.
Should we attack? They're six, three
of them are wounded.
It's time, my Bey, if you let me.
You don't know Abdurrahman Ghazi.
His beard is gray...
O The Healer.
But when it comes to
war, he's like a dragon.
Melik, tell the scouts.
Tell them to come here with warriors who
are capable of using the weapons well.
Zorba, keep an eye on them.
Will he be okay, Abdurrahman Ghazi?
Inshaallah.
But he's still bleeding...
we should cauterise.
O The Healer.
Cerkutay.
Balgay, you're wounded.
Osman kept his powder dry.
If we passed the hill...
we would have been under attack now.
How can Osman do that, Balgay?
We underestimated our enemy.
I swear on Kanbukan...
I swear on...
this fire.
My revenge will be hard.
How could Osman set this trap, Balgay?
Yannis!
Apparently, that old one also forgot
the Mongol's anger.
If he hadn't collaborated with Osman...
Osman would be bleeding now.
We ran out of soldiers, Balgay.
What will we do if Geyhatu hears that?
This is now my war.
If he faces me, I will kill Geyhatu.
We will go to Konya.
We will get new soldiers and come back.
When we come back...
we will kill everyone.
We will kill...
everyone in this country.
When you are a child...
you think your father is...
undefeated, the strongest.
You think you'll defeat everyone
when you grow up...
like your father.
You fight many battles...
but you lose against a beatiful one.
Thank my Lord, I can live this moment.
Gonca is waiting.
I should go.
Okay, daughter.
I know you have a lot of responsiblities.
You are always in a war.
However...
Not only that,
there's something else.
Tell me.
You are right.
You are right, mother.
What?
It is Bala.
What happened to Bala?
She changed.
She became someone else.
She says she is done for me.
- She tells me to look another Hatun.
- Did Bala tell you that?
Yes.
Bala told me.
Bala, who I put in the middle of my
heart, told that to me, mother.
Why, son, why did she?
I am looking for the answer.
I insisted...
I pushed her, but she doesn't talk.
There's something else,
but she won't tell me.
You can learn.
Tell me when you learn.
If it is a vaild reason,
Eyvallah ( it's okay)
If she says she doesn't love me anymore...
Eyvallah ( it's also okay)
Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Why did you do that to me?
You, how did you do that to our tribe,
our Ertuğrul Bey, Dündar Bey?
A great pain in the grave is waiting
for you.
I pity you.
You killed my son, my Batur.
Did you believe that?
Like you believed Alişar, Balgay, Sofia.
Ah, Dündar Bey, ah.
Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Kill me.
Or I will kill all of you.
I will take revenge of my son Batur.
Kill me.
Who sent you to where Osman set
a trap for Balgay? Tell me.
Tell me so that Osman can reveal the
game against us.
Then you can have the answers.
The game is Osman.
Osman.
It's Osman's command.
In order for him to atten his son's funeral
we'll take him to the graveyard tomorrow.
I will be with him.
- Inshallah he gets better until tomorrow.
- Inshallah.
Go, go away,cheeky Hatun, I see
blood while looking at you!
It's the blood you shed, Zöhre.
- You think of what you did.
- Enough!
Enough of your injustice!
Look, what is your daughter saying?
She says enough.
Enough already.
First Bala, now Gündüz.
This is not coincidence.
Speak!
You are out of your mind!
You are greedy for power!
Take it.
The tribe and Beyship is yours!
However, I will take revenge of my
Batur and Dündar!
What are you going to do, Zöhre?
Will you seek help from Mongols?
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
( in the name of God, the merciful and compassionate.)
He is capable of everything...
he fills our hearts with faith.
With the great Allah's 99 names.
My valiant fellows.
My tribe's almighty ones.
My uncle Dündar's Beyship has ended.
He bowed his head for Mongols.
Everybody saw that...
Not the ones who obey Mongols...
The ones who bow their head against no
one will be the future of Kayı!
Now, until my father returns, one of the
Kayı Beys will take his place.
I want that we choose a Bey...
who is going to be a servant for his
people, and be cruel to the enemy!
Osman Bey.
What you do is not in our tradition.
You spared our lives, Eyvallah (thank you)
However, just because you spared our lives,
we can't ignore our tradition.
Şahin Bey is right. The candidates should
be determiend beforehand.
Beys.
Look at the ones who talk about
tradiiton.
Demirci Bey.
Şahin Bey.
Who bowes their head for gold from
Mongols...
can't question our tradition.
We are talking about tradition, Bamsı Bey.
Neither our intention is bad,
nor what we say is wrong.
Don't abuse Osman Bey's mercy.
The format is right.
There will be a election.
We'll choose a Bey, and obey.
Şahin Bey, Demirci Bey.
Don't panic.
There wouldn't be impropriety
where my brother stands.
However, know that...
who disgraces the tradition
has nothing to do in this tribe.
My father set everything right.
Osman had to interfere!
My brother is gone.
My father is gone!
Will you take my mother now?
This is your time to be seen nice
in Osman's sight.
Kill me and my mother.
You can be the new owners.
Shame on you.
The more someone is angry the worse
her heart is.
She becoems rude, Aygül Hatun.
I wish you could hear what you say.
Ah, ah.
Now, I will say it directly, Zöhre Hatun.
There will be Batur's funeral.
If you wish to be a mother and
attend to the funeral...
I can get you out of here.
Tell me.
Are you coming or not?
What do you mean coming or not?
Of course I will come.
Of course I will!
Okay then.
I know your heart is burning.
I know your situation.
However, if you wish to attend
Batur's funeral...
you need to speak.
We understand, we know that you
are involved in this.
We need further information.
Tell me, then we can go to the funeral,
ha?
Speak.
Come on, Zöhre.
Give it away.
Be with your son.
Tell me.
I wanted to save it.
I wanted to protect my children, my Bey.
I did it to protect my tribe.
Tell me.
I went to Balgay.
Mother.
What have you done?
I asked, your mother talked, Aygül.
You heard.
I have had enough.
You can tell the rest to your daughter.
Gonca.
What does Bala Hatun worry about?
Tell me. She told Osman to look for another woman.
Is this because of her problems?
It's because of her wound which she's
received in Mongol attack.
She won't have any children from now on.
Now that the intention is to choose
a bey to correct the law...
...then everybody should speak.
Now, Kayı Tent is not the same as before.
We have a lot of flocks and products.
We need a bey that needs to
carry out both trade and morals.
My candidate is...
...Gunduz Bey.
He is sincere, graceful and his
decisions are proper.
My candidate is...
...Gunduz Bey.
We've got over all those problems
thanks to his determination.
We've got over tough circumstances
thanks to his skillfulness.
I like Gunduz Bey so much and
appreciate him a lot.
But I think Osman Bey should be
the bey of all Kayı Tents.
My candidate is Osman Bey.
I agree with Sahin Bey and Demirci Bey.
My candidate is Gunduz Bey.
My Osman...
My Osman is the flood.
And Gunduz is the soil.
My Osman is the water.
My Gunduz is the bread.
My Osman is the fire.
My Gunduz is the coolness.
But...
...bey is such a person that
he foresees the future
Bey is such a person that he has
blood on both side of the sword.
So...
...my candidate is Osman.
Osman bey.
Bamsi Bey.
The right is speaking.
My candidate is Osman Bey.
We stopped.
He ran.
We just looked.
He hit.
There had been occupations.
We all obeyed them.
He rose against them.
He has been our hope, our freedom and
our honour.
He isn't just a brother for me...
...he is my fellow always.
I see the ability that my Father had,
not in me.
I see it in him.
I know and believe that...
...the prosperity of Kayı is Osman.
My candidate is...
...Osman.
Duty is both hard and holy.
My brother is both careful and	moderate.
In this tough process, we need
a fair bey who foresees the future...
...who is calm, graceful
and acts according to his morals.
My brother Gunduz Bey...
...has the ability to differentiate
the black snake on the black stone...
the white material in white milk.
My candidate is...
...my brother Gunduz bey.
I renounce from all votes.
My brother Gunduz bey is
the bey of Ertugrul Gazi.
I wish best for your Tent, my brother.
Thanks, brother.
I wish you will bring luck to soldiers,
Gunduz Bey.
Thanks, Samsa.
If you excuse me,
I want to go my tent
I need to check it.
You can go, Samsa Bey.
I wish best for your Tent, Gunduz Bey.
Thanks.
I wish best for your Tent, my son.
Thanks, Bamsi Bey.
Batur.
In the first day he joined our case,
his bravery was nearly led him to death.
Our road
was separate.
But Allah is witness, his intention
wasn't bad.
If he hadn't stand behind his father,
his ending wouldn't be like that.
I'll cut the heads of those
who did it to you, myself.
I promise.
Son.
You will take your revenge.
You will.
But from who?
Who did this treachery?
I don't know who planned it
now.
But those who set up traps think that they
reached their goal.
They wanted you to be
responsible for this job.
And they got what they wanted.
I'll ruin all the
traps they set.
Now that they don't act properly,
I will act like them.
Is it the reason why you hide that Dundar
is alive, my son?
Let those who set up
traps believe they are winning!
Let them believe more.
I'll disintegrate this foggy air with a wolf
claw where even devil acts like a Muslim.
Till that day, let them know
that I killed Batur.
When the time is over...
...I'll kill and cut the heads of
those evils.
What about Dundar?
Dundar bey has the right to be here
when his son is buried, Bamsi Bey.
I reported.
Abdullah Efendi will bring him to the tent
before the funeral.
Thanks, Osman.
Thanks.
My bey.
Balgay escaped.
The only way Balgay can escape
is his death.
He can't get rid of me.
You ruined.
You exhausted yourself.
Don't do it anymore.
I can't bear to...
...be silence when he speaks...
...go away when he is approaching...
...and offend him deliberately every time,
Gonca.
That doesn't work like that.
That doesn't work like that, Bala.
If you don't say it to Osman,
I will.
You're not gonna say anything.
We'll go from here.
It will be better to not be here.
What's happened, my mother?
Why are you sad, explain to me?
I will, my son.
Is it about Bala?
Tell me, mother.
Bala has a big trouble, my son.
She lives with the hardest
trouble any woman ever can have.
What's that?
Explain.
Explain, mother.
Don't worry me.
The wound she got
when Mongol attacked...
...is the reason of coldness
between you, my son.
It isn't because she doesn't
love you.
As she fears that she can't give birth
to a baby, she spoke you like that.
But...
It is not certain.
I can't leave her
just because of this.
I know, my son.
I know.
Your love is as strong as
your heart.
The caretaker of
Bala told her...
...she shouldn't give up from believing
Allah after the wound she got.
She won't give up surely.
But she hesitates a lot.
Nobody knows how much she got
worried and thought about it.
I wish I forced her more.
I wish I knew it before.
She may have thought about it
a lot.
But now it's the problem
both of you.
You can sacrifice your life for
each other let alone love each other.
I know.
You'll get rid of it eventually.
You again made me a favour
as my mother.
You relieved me.
You learned the truth for me.
May Allah don't allow us
to be far apart, my mother.
Don't allow us.
Walk!
Where are you taking me?
Why isn't there anyone?
They went to revenge Balgay.
How?
How dare they?
You don't know Osman Bey.
Everything happened thanks to you
and Yannis, Sofia.
Walk!
Traitor Salvador!
Salvador.
You are free now, princess.
Where is Helen and Andreas?
Andreas died when he was trying to escape.
Helen is waiting for us.
Salvador.
I will never forget it.
You get just your desserts.
Dervish.
Let's take Helen and go
back to the castle.
Who are you?
Your death.
I've seen a lot of brave people wishing
to be my death.
But all of them are dead.
Abdurrahman Gazi!
Alps!
Allahu Akbar!
Kılıç!
Erkut!
My valiant!
Abdurrahman Gazi!
Kılıç!
Erkut!
I bear witness that...
there is none worthy of worship except Allah...
Alişar!
You, huh?
Alişar! You, huh?
Leaving Dundar bey for such jackals like
you doesn't suit to banner lord like me.
Instead of hiding behind your soldiers...
... come and fight with me like
a real man. Come, Alisar!
Abdurrahman Gazi.
As long as you have such a heart,
everything will be alright eventually.
- Welcome, my girl.
- Thank you, Selcan Hatun.
I was going to take some syrup.
Let me prepare it. We will drink together.
Like I don't love anybody except you...
...I don't have the intention of
looking for someone else, Bala.
You are my blessing.
Just be.
Having a child is the will of Allah.
As we love each other like that...
...the power of a dagger wound
can't tear us apart, Bala.
Osman.
Don't.
No.
You will have children.
I'm not suitable for you.
Are you not suitable for me?
Bala! Being without you breaks me
down.
Being without you is the biggest
problem between now and tomorrow.
You are my strength and power.
You're the light of my road.
You...
... are my dream. My love.
After gaining my sheikh consent...
... having a family with you
is my biggest dream.
You're my blind love, Hatun.
If Allah doesn't give us
a child, I am okay with that.
I am okay with everything as long
as I'm with you.
Tell me.
Are you okay with it too?
I accept everything as long
as you do, Osman.
May I come in, my Bey?
Come in, Boran.
Excuse me.
My Bey, a valiant wants to see you.
He says it is important.
He may come in.
Where are you headed to, Osman Bey?
To Kızıl Elma.
The Elders are waiting for you, Osman Bey.
Your duty is important.
We have failed, Master.
Forgive us.
What's important is that you're still
here, my daughter.
You made an agreement with
Osman for me, Master.
You shouldn't have done it.
I can turn these lands into
a sea of blood for you.
Where is Andreas?
They...
They killed him, Master.
What is that called?
Stupidity? Or betrayal?
Doesn't matter.
Either of its price is death.
Master Yannis! Salvador saved our lives by
killing Edebali's dervishes.
Princess is right.
We're alive thanks to Salvador.
Plus, he was injured while
fighting beside us.
Go to your room, son.
Wait for my word about your reward.
Salvador is lying.
But Master!
One day, the rat in the church
make a decision after...
... they are tired of
the cat bothering them.
They will hang a bell to the cat's neck...
... and they will know before he comes.
So they will live peacefully.
But they need a rat both brave and
stupid enough to hang the bell.
Osman found that stupid rat.
- Will you kill Salvador, Master?
- No.
I will kill the cat.
For that, I will use that stupid
and brave rat.
How will you do that, Master?
I will promote Salvador to
Commander of Kulucahisar?
Balgay is calm for now.
But when he's available, he'll come at us.
We need to increase
the Tent's safety measures.
Thankfully, people trust us and
they have united once again.
Now Balgay knows what is waiting for him.
It's a good thing that Osman didn't kill
Dündar Bey after everything he did.
Because establishing the unity you're
talking about would take time.
Correct. Correct.
- May I come in, Gündüz Bey?
- Come in, brother.
Here, my brother.
Brother. We need to find Balgay.
He lost everything.
He probably will escape to Konya.
If we don't prevent it,
he will come back more powerful than ever.
What should we do?
What do you have in mind, Osman?
If you allow it, I want to set off
with Konur and Boran.
I will catch Balgay before
he goes to Konya.
What if you can't catch him?
What if he arrives at Konya?
Death doesn't care about
geography, Bamsı Bey.
Then I will take his life in Konya.
Nice.
Keep an eye on the castle.
Sıddık is still on duty.
He's waiting to hear from us.
When the time comes, we'll fly the Kayı
flag on Kulucahisar, if Allah permits.
Praise be! Don't look back, my valiant!
Good luck!
Thank you, Bamsı Bey.
Before the funeral, Abdurrahman Gazi
will bring Dündar Bey to the Tent.
He should say his last words to his son
with his wife before he is exiled.
Brother. Don't tell anyone that
Dündar Bey is alive.
I can only find out who played tricks on
us this way.
Excuse me.
We're going to a battle, Sıddık brother.
Osman Bey's orders.
- Listen to me carefully.
- I'd die for Osman Bey's order!
What do I need to do, Boran Alp?
You will kidnap Sofia and
give her to Yannis.
So they'll trust you more.
When we arrive at the castle's gates
with flags of conquest...
... you will be the one who
opens the castle's doors.
Allah almighty, my duty is hard,
my burden is heavy.
Don't let me be ashamed to Osman Bey,
and Osman Bey to Mohammad's people.
Dear Allah, don't let Osman Bey and
his fellows be humiliated to infidels.
Grant such a victory to them that
the oppressed be delighted.
If you please, let Sıddık, this servant
of yours, be sacrificed.
For the glory of İslam,
I'm willing to give up my spirit.
As long as my life is sacrificed
for Muslims.
You blessed me. In the end, allow me
to fall as a martyr, my Allah.
Amen.
Prince Salvador!
Master Yannis is waiting for you.
I'm coming.
Thousands of horseman will come after me.
Just wait.
Osman Bey will come.
- Zorba.
- Yes, my Bey?
Tell my soldiers to get
on with their duties.
Gather those who are loyal to me.
Tell them to come to the mansion tonight.
Banner Lord Alişar Bey
will be having a great feast.
As you wish, my Bey.
Melik.
Let the Tents know that I'm once again
the Banner Lord with the order of Geyhatu.
If they refuse...
... show them Geyhatu's commandment.
- What if they resist?
- Make them worse than Balgay.
They should know that I bashed Balgay's
head in. And they should act accordingly.
And now for Kayıs...
I will visit them myself.
As you wish, my Bey.
You made them steal my gold...
... and made them come to the verge
of a battle with Kulucahisar.
Is this how you protect the lands
I trusted you with?
- Zorba.
- Yes, my Bey?
Prepare my clothes.
We're done with Balgay for now.
Now I need to get even with
that woman called Sofia.
- Did you put Dündar Bey in his room?
- I did, my Bey.
I'm very happy. I told you. Your love is
different from those which fade away.
I didn't want anything for myself
until today.
If it's destiny, if we're
going to settle down with Osman...
... my only wish will be to
give him a child, Gonca.
If Allah permits, my Bala.
That will happen too if Allah permits.
May I come in?
Come in, Osman Bey.
I was about to go to Selcan Hatun.
Excuse me.
Now that I've seen that smile...
Even if my path ends at the end
of the world, I won't worry.
What path, Osman? What is it?
I can't leave that Balgay dog alive.
If I can't pursue him,
he will come back stronger.
I hope the Mongol won't be big trouble.
If I can't take Balgay's life,
this issue will grow bigger.
If I catch him on the road, there, if not,
in Konya, I will kill him eventually.
Don't leave the Tent...
... if you don't have
to until I return.
As you say.
Don't worry about us.
For the love of Allah, be careful.
Oh...
Are you afraid something
might happen to me?
May Allah take your pain, ache,
troubles from you and give them to me.
No. I wouldn't say "Amin"
to a prayer like that.
If you are okay...
... the rest is irrelevant.
I don't know how, but when you smile,
I become much more powerful.
I feel like I would crush the
mountains if they ask me to.
Farewell, keep your love
and prayers with me.
Both my prayers and my love is with you.
May Allah watch over you.
Dündar Bey, are you okay?
I will host you in my mansion,
worthy of your pride, don't worry.
Why did you- Why did you
bring me here, Alişar?
I need to go to my Tent at once.
Why, so that Osman can
finish what he started?
Osman entered the Tent with Samsa's soldiers
and made Gündüz sit on his father's throne.
- What?
- His brother will be a puppet for him.
Until he becomes the Bey of the Tent.
I own the Tent, Alişar Bey,
he can't do that.
He told everyone that you died.
Damn the day that I informed
Geyhatu and saved his life.
I should've let Balgay take his life!
Dündar Bey, Dündar Bey,
don't lose yourself.
That was Osman's intentions
from the start.
Then why didn't he kill me?
Who knows what foul plans
does he have in his mind.
Now, I will go and take Zöhre Hatun and
Aygül from the caged tent he put in.
You should rest now.
Zöhre.
My daughter.
Let them all know you as dead.
Even if we can't know what they'll do to
Zöhre Hatun and Aygül if they find out.
Isn't that right?
My daughter.
Salvador, brave warrior of Catalonia.
Rule with our Holy Father's justice,
and our Holy Mother's mercy.
I declare you the
Commander of Kulucahisar!
By the Father, Son and the Holy Spirit.
If I stray away from our Holy Father's way
may this sword cut my flesh and bones.
Alişar Bey is here, Princess,
he is waiting for you.
Inform Master Yannis.
Amen.
I swear to be loyal to our Holy Father and
fight our enemies until my last breath!
Commander Salvador!
Alişar Bey is here, sir.
I only got one question to
you, answer it correctly.
What did Osman offer to
your father to betray Balgay?
I am sure it wasn't
your miserable life.
You know everything, I am sure
you know the answer to that too.
Laws of Genghis Khan,
and the Dagger.
And you...
How could you be so brave to come here?
Geyhatu ordered me to give this
letter to you as the Banner Lord.
So, he wants the Laws and the Dagger.
In exchange for what?
Osman's death, and your life.
Osman crushed Balgay himself.
You know he'll be back for revenge.
How could I...
... trust Geyhatu...
... or you?
Your scent is killing me, Hatun.
But...
... you can't even imagine how bad
you'll smell when you're dead.
I know the things you did behind me.
I am ready to forget everything
if you are with me.
We will both win if I kill
Osman and give Geyhatu...
... Laws and the Dagger.
Osman killed Dündar.
He took the Tent with his brother.
Now...
... tell me...
... what do you have in your hands?
Dündar is alive...
... only I can keep him, his stubborn
wife and his beautiful daughter alive.
We will give Dündar his Tent back.
We will do this together.
How can I trust Geyhatu?
Geyhatu wants to marry Princess Adelfia to
improve trade relations with Byzantine.
Princess is on her way to Konya.
Now we have one mutual enemy, Sofia.
Osman.
You are either with me,
or six feet under.
Princess.
Free me, Selcan Hatun, it's my right
to go to my brother's funeral.
If this was about rights, my Batur
wouldn't deserve to die, Aygül.
Listen carefully, Zöhre.
You won't be able to live in
this Tent after what you did.
Attend to your son's funeral,
then take your daughter and go.
Go to the Mongols that you beg.
What is the meaning of this?
Punishment for treachery
is death in Oghuz Tradition.
You should pray Gündüz Bey for his mercy.
The ones who call us traitors
don't look to themselves.
It's easy to call us traitors.
Enough!
You stubborn, shameless dog!
This is all because of your greed!
You couldn't stand to Osman, you even
went to Balgay and begged him!
You lost your son but
still, you didn't stop. Enough!
Selcan Hatun, stop.
Free me.
Go to your son and do your duty.
Look at him, if you still have a
face to look, say your farewell. Hurry!
You didn't disappoint us
with our faith in you, Osman Bey.
You've repelled Balgay.
War is ours, victory is Allah's.
Thank Allah, now Balgay has seen that the
Turks will never surrender to anyone too.
But it will get harder
from now on, know that.
If I don't destroy Balgay, he will
come back with a bigger force.
Our issue is bigger than that.
Now, our fight will be even harsher.
Now, listen to me carefully, son.
While we are making moves, the
devil's army attacks without stopping.
Geyhatu has declared Alişar
as the banner lord again.
Because he is not in
good terms with Balgay.
Because of Genghis Khan's Laws,
Balgay disappointed Geyhatu.
It's clear that he will come back and
haunt the Turkish Tents with this rage.
We've finished Balgay's courage.
Now he is in no place to spread fear.
We will fight him with everything we got.
We will continue to do so.
Thank you, there is
no doubt about that.
Now we have more important
business with Balgay.
Princess Adelfa, who
lives in Constantinopolis...
... will be married to the Mongolian
governor Geyhatu by the Emperor.
That means...
... a Mongolian-Byzantine alliance.
Alliance for them,
doomsday for the Turks.
The Tents in the edges will
be caught in the crossfire.
Osman Bey, you need to prevent
this marriage from happening.
Princess Adelfa doesn't
want this marriage.
But what's important is taking Princess
from the agents of Geyhatu.
Are their route set?
They will go through Nicea to probably
Eskihisar, then from there, to Konya.
You need to do this with your life!
I will do what I can.
I will crush the traps that Mongols
and Byzantine set for us.
Thank you.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com